go-today.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy for go-today | Vacation Packages

## Privacy Policy

Go-today (the "Company", "we", "our", or "us") Privacy Policy sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it. Our Privacy Policy applies to you and your use of our website, other applications, platforms or channels, available now or created in the future, which are owned or operated by the Company and through which we make our products and services available (collectively, the "Sites"). In all your dealings with us you must ensure that others you represent are aware of the content of our Privacy Policy and consent to your acting on their behalf. 

### INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

### Your Information

This refers to a combination of information such as your name, contact details, travel preferences and special needs/disabilities/dietary requirements that you supply us or is supplied to us, including your social preferences, interests and activities and any information about other persons you represent (such as those on your booking). Your information is collected when you request information from us, contact us (and vice versa), make a booking, use our Sites and any other engagement we or our business partners have with you. 

We will update your information whenever we can to keep it current, accurate and complete. 

### Our Use of Your Information

(1) For the purpose of providing you with our services, including your flight, holiday, security, incident/accident management or insurance, etc., we may disclose and process your information to third parties. In order for you to travel abroad, it may be mandatory (as required by government authorities at the point(s) of departure and/or destination) to disclose and process your information for immigration, border control, security and anti-terrorism purposes, or any other purposes which they determine appropriate. Some countries will only permit travel if you provide your advance passenger data (for example Caricom API and US secure flight data). These requirements may differ depending on your destination and you are advised to check. Even if not mandatory, we may exercise our discretion to assist where appropriate. 

(2) We may collect, and disclose to others, the information you provide to us and our group companies and brands for business purposes and also third-party companies and our third-party service providers for the purposes set forth below in this Section 2. If you do provide us with your information, we will only share it for the purposes described at the point of collection. We will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of the Company for any other purpose unless (a) you expressly authorize us to do so, or; (b) it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services to you or; (c) it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements; (d) it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of the Company or the merger of Company into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, bankruptcy or like transaction in which the Company is not the survivor; (e) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, administration, service, customer care, quality and improvement related activity, business management and operation, risk assessment/management, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, social media, reviews, advertising and marketing, loyalty programs, profiling customer purchasing preferences, activities and trends, dispute resolution/litigation, credit checking and debt collection, or; (f) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law. 

_If you do not agree to Our Use of Your Information above, we cannot engage/do business with you or accept your booking._

### Marketing Material

(1) Using your information, we may from time to time contact you with or make available to you (directly or indirectly) information on offers of goods and services, brochures, new products, forthcoming events or competitions from our holiday divisions and our group companies or third-parties as set above ("Our Use of Your Information"). We will tailor the information you receive or see; this will enable us to make available to you more personalised and relevant communications. We may use innovative technologies and work with our third-party business partners to achieve this. 

(2) We will assume you agree to email when you make an e-booking or provide us with your email in other situations such as in-store, competitions, promotions, prize draws and social media. 

(3) If you do not wish to receive such information or would like to change your preferences, please refer to the "Your Rights" section of this Privacy Policy below. 

### Your Rights

Upon request via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone, we will provide you a summary of your information retained by the Company. As allowed by law and consistent with our applicable business partner agreements, you may modify, correct, change, or request the Company to delete or update information that you have supplied to us through the Sites by contacting the Company via postal mail to: Go-today, 19909 120th Ave NE Suite 202, Bothell, WA 98011; or, to the extent available, you can amend your previous preference either: (i) directly on our website(s); (ii) by using our "unsubscribe email" available on every marketing email sent by the Company; (iii) by opting-out of personalised emails; or (iv) by referring to our literature containing instructions on how to opt-out of marketing communications. Once properly notified by you, we will take steps to stop using your information in this way. 

### Foreign Controls

Our Sites are intended for and directed to consumers in the United States of America. If you are visiting from the European Economic Area ("EEA") or other regions or countries with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information about you to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as the EEA or the non-U.S. region or country from which you have transmitted your information. By providing us with your information you consent to: the transfer of information about you, including information to the U.S.; and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)

Our Sites gather certain broad, Non-PII about use of our Sites, including the number of unique visitors to the Sites, the frequency with which they visit the Sites and the services preferred by those visitors on the Sites. The Company looks at the data regarding use of the Sites in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. We gather this Non-PII data so we can learn, for example, which pages of the Sites are the most and least viewed by visitors and which third-party websites are referring visitors to the Sites. The Non-PII data helps the Company determine the extent to which visitors use certain parts of the Sites and allows us to tailor the Sites in the future. In connection with these activities, the Company may use the following standard technology tools ("Technology Tools") to collect information: 

### Log Information:

When you visit the Sites and view content provided by the Company on the Sites, we automatically collect and store certain information in our server logs. This type of information includes your IP address information, web pages which have been viewed by a you in the form of Session ID data, the data and time of your Site visits, domain type, system activity, hardware, analytics data including device type and unique Client ID data, user interactions across devices, device settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL. 

### Cookies:

A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. We uses cookies to, among other things, identify your computer during a particular visit to the Sites and analyze your behavior during a particular visit. We does not store personal or sensitive information in cookies. Most web browsers provide you with the ability to accept or decline cookies, as well as to be warned each time a cookie is being sent. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to take advantage of all aspects of the Sites. 

### Pixel Tags:

Pixel tags, also known as web beacons or clear GIFs, help the Company better manage content on the Sites by informing it of what content is effective. Pixel tags are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on web pages. 

### IP Addresses:

The Company collects and analyzes traffic on the Sites by keeping track of the IP addresses of its visitors. An IP address is the unique numeric identifier assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet service provider, your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message. 

### USE OF TECHNOLOGY TOOLS

If our contact and dealing with you is via our Sites, cookiesthe above mentioned technology tools may be used. To find out more specific information about the types of Technology Tools used on our Sites, how we use them, how to disable them or how to change your preferences and more, please see our Cookies Policy. **_By using our Sites, you consent to our use of cookies._**

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our Sites may contain links to third party websites or micro-sites not controlled or owned by us. For example, reference sites or ancillary products and services sites or websites owned by our sister companies. It is your responsibility to check the status of these sites before using them. Please read their applicable terms and conditions carefully. 

### CHILDREN UNDER 13

Our Sites are not directed to persons under the age of 13. We do not collect information from children under 13 other than as when necessary to comply with the law or for safety reasons. If you are under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using our Sites. Furthermore, we may restrict entries to any contests, sweepstakes or promotions to entrants who are at least 18 years of age. 

### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

This notification is required under California law. Under California law, California residents may opt-out of the Company disclosing personal information about them to third parties for their marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and do not want us to disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes, please contact us by using the details provided under the "Your Rights" section above. Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request a copy of such information, please contact us using the details provided under the "Your Rights" section above, and we will respond within 30 days as required by law. 

### SECURITY STATEMENT

No data transmissions over the Internet are completely secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the Internet. You transmit such information at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. We use reasonable efforts to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach or other unintended, unauthorized or criminal activity. 

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Any changes to this Policy will be either posted on our website, brochure and/or made available on request. In the event we materially change the way in which we use your information, we will provide you with at least 30 days' notice and ask you to affirmatively accept the changes. 

_Privacy Policy: v February 2017_
